如果你打开这个文档，你能看到
If you open up the documentation, you can see a
一些常见屏宽的例子。这里给了一些怎样
couple of examples of typical screen widths. Then it suggests how
设置Layout文件夹的一些建议，以至你能
you can setup your layout folders, so that you can
为平板电脑和手机创建不同的用户界面
have a different main activity layout for tablets versus for handsets.
这里我们限制了平板电脑的最小屏宽
And here we define tablets as having a smallest width
是600dp。为了进一步定制用户界面，
of at least 600 dp. To customize the UI further, we
我们可以再创建一个layout-sw720dp文件夹。这样我可以
can create a layout-sw720dp folder. That way, we can have a
针对10寸平板，7寸平板和手机
different main activity layout for ten inch tablets versus for seven
设置不同的用户界面。现在回到
inch tablets versus for handsets. So back to
我们的测试。我们需要定义activity_main.xml
our quiz. We need to define activity_main.xml file in
在默认Layout文件夹里，这样我们可以完成
our base layout folder so that we can accomplish
手机的界面设置。这个界面设置会被应用到
this layout on the phone. This layout applies to
手机横向和纵向两张情况，所以不需要
both phone, portrait, and landscape, so we don't need
在layout-land文件夹里单独创建一个界面设置文件
a special version of the layout in the layout-land
我们需要在layout-sw600dp文件夹里创建
folder. We do also need to declare activity_main.xml
activity_main.xml。这样它会覆盖
in the layout-sw600dp folder. That way it will override
单面板界面而使用双面板界面。当设备屏宽
the one pane UI and use a two pane UI in this case. It will be
大于600dp时，这个界面配置
picked up on devices that have greater than
就会被使用到。
600 dp in both width and height. That
也就是7寸平板和10寸平板
means seven inch and ten inch devices in
无论是横向或是纵向时。最后
both portrait and landscape mode. And lastly, we
我们实际上不需要layout-sw720dp，因为我们没有不同的配置
don't need layout-sw720dp because we don't have different
给7寸平板和10寸平板
layouts for seven inch versus ten inch devices.